depositfiles.net 2017-07-22

# Mobile DepositFiles

Privacy policy:

**A substantial amount information is collected during rendering services DepositFiles in ordinary course of business. DepositFiles shall do its best to safeguard your privacy within the legal boundaries.**

  1. **Information not considered private:**

There is certain information which is not confidential and thus subject to third party review and automated filtering to ensure observance of DepositFiles User Agreement and supplemental policies:

    1. **Public materials.**

Any end-user materials which is accessible by means of publically available URL (e.g. http://depositfiles.com/files/*********);

    2. **Public information.**

Any information you wishfully elect to disclose to public or which has been known to public prior to being collected by DepositFiles.

  2. **Private information.**

The following information held by DepositFiles is confidential and undisclosed unless stated otherwise:

    1. **Personal information.**

Any personal information not made publically available through your action or inaction - is confidential and is not subject to disclosure or filtering upon presumption of fair use;

    2. **Cookies use.**

You explicitly authorize DepositFiles to create and store cookies at your computer. Please read DepositFiles Cookie Policy for detailed information;

    3. **Page indexing.**

DepositFiles does not index data or pages to be available in human-readable form and proceeds with reasonable actions to stop any third parties (e.g. search engines) from indexing independently;

    4. **IP addresses.**

IP address of your browser is detected due to the use of Internet-protocols. Such IP address is stored by DepositFiles servers for internal use (usage registration, optimal downloads use, statistics etc.);

    5. **E-mail.**

DepositFiles servers store and sort user e-mails for the purposes of registration and statistics. DepositFiles does not lease, sell, or provide your e-mails to any third parties;

    6. **Safe operation.**

We have taken the security measures at the server's physical location to protect from loss, incorrect usage, or change of information provided to us by the users of the service. Files, saved at the servers of DepositFiles can be accessible only to DepositFiles staff members or via a URL initially provided to the uploader. Any files saved by our service are deleted (I) after a certain term of disuse; (II) for violation of User Agreement, its supplemental agreements or any applicable legislation; or (III) deleted via a special URL initially provided to the uploader;

    7. **Financial information.**

Any financial transfers between you and DepositFiles are handled by third party, payment services. Your payment details are disclosed to such third parties for the aim of completion of each transaction. The security and non-disclosure of such information is handled by such third parties under their current policies. DepositFiles does not sort or store numbers or any information related to your banking card.

  3. **Advertisers' access to information.**

Certain third parties may have access to your non-personally identifiable information as follows:

    1. **Impression of advertisements.**

Advertisements located on our website can be posted and/or hosted by a third party, advertiser or agents. These persons can use the information regarding your visits obtained due to common use of Internet-protocols (geographical location, IP, language and other information automatically disclosed by your browser) to place an advertisement of goods and services that might be interest you. Any information collected at the pages owned by third parties is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

    2. **Third-party behavioral advertising practice.**

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) and Networking Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

  4. **DISCLOSURE.**

DEPOSITFILES MAY DISCLOSE ANY CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION IN CASE IT BECOMES NECESSARY TO DEFEND ITS JURIDICAL RIGHTS.

IN CASE YOUR ACTIONS LEAD TO SUSPICION OF TANGIBLE OR ASSUMED SABOTEUR ACTIONS OR POSES A POTENTIAL THREAT TO ANY PERSON'S PHYSICAL SAFETY OR ANY OTHER GRAVE CRIME, ALL YOUR KNOWN INFORMATION (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO PERSONAL DETAILS, IP ADDRESSES, PAYMENT DATA) MAY BE DISCLOSED TO LAW ENFORCEMENT ORGANIZATIONS AND/OR INTERNET SERVICE PROVIDER WITHOUT PRIOR NOTICE.

IN CASE OF ANY EVIDENCE OF DISTRIBUTION OF THE FILES CONTAINING MATERIALS WHICH APPEAR INVOLVING CHILD EXPLOITATION, THE ACCOUNT BELONGING TO THE USER WHO UPLOADED SUCH FILES WILL BE IMMEDIATELY DELETED AND ALL KNOWN INFORMATION (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO PERSONAL DETAILS, IP ADDRESSES, PAYMENT DATA) WILL BE DIRECTED TO THE NATIONAL CENTER FOR MISSING & EXPLOITED CHILDREN AND/OR HOTLINE COMBATING CHILD PORNOGRAPHY ON THE INTERNET, AS WELL AS LAW ENFORCEMENT ORGANIZATIONS AND/OR MEMBERS OF INTERNET SERVICE PROVIDERS WITHOUT PRIOR NOTICE.

DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION CAN BE LAWFUL AS A RESULT OF A LEGAL PROCESS.
